This isn't war. It's a game.
The Wall is a war, thriller, drama film directed by Doug Liman.
An American sniper and his spotter engage in a deadly
cat-and-mouse game with an Iraqi sniper.
Isaac, played by Aaron Taylor-Johnson.
Matthews, played by John Cena.
Juba (voice), played by Laith Nakli.
The Wall is a 2017 American war thriller film directed by
Doug Liman and written by Dwain Worrell.
The film follows two American soldiers (Aaron Taylor-Johnson
and John Cena) trapped by an Iraqi sniper.
Produced by Amazon Studios, it was released on May
12, 2017, by Roadside Attractions.
The film received mixed reviews from critics and audiences and
grossed $4.5 million against a $3 million budget.
The film explores themes of sniper, helicopter, iraq, murder, soldier.
The tone is emotional and intense.